

Falmouth, Cornwall, United Kingdom

■ harry.bd11@gmail.com | HDonovan96 | MeachAbyss

Summary

I am an avid programmer and competent and passionate producer, with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, agile methodology, and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have lead teams which have published to both Itch and Steam, always with a focus on maintaining healthy and flexible working practices. My ideal position would be junior producer role, with a strong focus on growing my skills and experience so I could progress to a more senior position.

Skills

- · Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Sprint Planning, Trello
- · Version Control: Git
- · Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4
- · Languages: C#, C++, Latex

Published Games

Carma - Producer & Team Lead

Unity 2019.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1603990/CARMA/)

Published June 2021

- · Worked with a multidisciplinary team to bring Carma from concept to published game • Planned sprints and development milestones using Agile
- Worked with the team to remove any blockers and streamline development pipelines
- · Focused on maintaining team health and reinforcing healthy working practices
- Handled setting up Steam store and updating builds

Yvaga Station - Team Lead & Programmer

Unity 2018.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO ITCH.IO (HTTPS://DAYLUKE.ITCH.IO/YVAGA-STATION)

Published May 2020

- Presented a concept pitch to in order to continue development past prototype stage
- Implemented asymmetric multiplayer game using PUN2 package for networking
- · Designed and implemented a modular custom movement system to expand on the options available to the player

Programming Projects

Pacman Al

Unity 2019.4.1

December 2020 - January 2021

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/HDONOVAN96/PACMANAI

- University project to implement behaviour trees for Pacman ghosts
- Designed and implemented three unique behaviors Scout, Guard, and Pursuit
- · Agents designed to work together Scout relays players position to other agents while avoiding conflict with the player
- · Implemented agent 'memory', so agents remember the position of pills and the player and act only on this info

Infinity - Battle Royal

Unreal Engine 4.22.3

May 2020 - August 2020

- Designed code structure for complex weapon system with loot spawning, weapon modifications, and fire modes
- · Systems designed to interface with a custom network designed by another programmer
- Implemented majority of the systems, including setting up recoil so it could be driven by IK systems

Education

Falmouth University BSc Computing For Games

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - June 2022

- · Worked with a multi-discipline team to bring several games through a full development cycle
- · Learned about and improved upon creating neat, maintainable code through commenting and UML diagrams
- · Participated in modules including creating a custom physical controller and designing an audio generation tool
- · Received and responded to feedback from concept pitches, module evaluations and regular game progress reviews I am involved with a peer-assisted learning programme (PASS) designed to help teach new students vital problem solving skills
- · I am also active with helping other students with general, programming, and version control questions outside of this role

Work Experience

Director Falmouth, Cornwall

GLASS NOMAD GAMES

March 2021 - Current

- Started a company to publish video games my team and I were developing
- Handled registration and set up with services such as Steam

Senior Ambassador Falmouth, Cornwall

FXPLUS

- June 2020 Current
- Increased responsibility for the smooth running of events
- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

Student Ambassador Falmouth, Cornwall

FXPLUS

October 2019 - June 2020

- Involved in the running of university events and open days
- · This includes discussing the course with potential students and leading group tours around the campus
- I have also spoken on an online Q&A panel as part of this role

Extracurricular Activity

PASS Leader Falmouth, United Kingdom

FALMOUTH UNIVERSITY

September 2020 - January 2021

- · Planned and lead regular Peer Assisted Support Scheme (PASS) sessions for first year students in our department
- · Sessions were student led, with us tailoring sessions around what students wished to cover
- Sessions focused on common problems and soft skills